Now listen, yo!
People put your guns up
First I'll run dat
Run around and shoot them
Brand new sound, yes still survival
Here comes the sound boy, live in this world
Intelligence, strength, and luck are swirling, flow
My swelled mind is candid
One punch to Banner in Savannah
An easy knockout, bam bam bam
One time for your mind, live through this
Around the world
It haunts me, the pain of the past
Around the noble god are borrowed things
When the seed that's sown flowers, whose is it
Live and fire the arrow of faith, more more more
There is no peace where you're going
Come on, stand up, don't give up the fight
Now, yes, this instant, die die die
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
Big shooter, living fast, blazing
Beat you up, cut it open, break
Shot shooter, he lived fast, crazy
Adjust your sights at point-blank range, break
I'm sorry.
（岸本(きしもと)）ごめん
なんか いつも違うこと言ってるね
I know I say something different every time.
But this is not the time
to be saying you can't shoot.
でも もう
“撃てない”とか言ってる場合じゃ
You're right...
（加藤(かとう)）そうだな
（計(けい)）“全員で帰る” …だろう？
We're all going back together, right?
Yeah...
（加藤）ああ！
（トマオ）坊主 やべえよ
That priest... He's not gonna make it!
Let's get that alien first!
（計）とりあえず
あっちから片づけようぜ
Yeah, let's do it!
（加藤）そうだな
Namu Amida Butsu!
（徳川）南無阿弥陀仏！
It stopped!
止まった！ 経を唱えると
おとなしくなるのか？
Do Buddhist scriptures calm them down?!
Stop it, you fools!
バカ者！ やめんか！
こやつらは
経を唱えれば静まるのだ！
Reciting Buddhist scriptures
can calm them down!
そんなはずは ねえ！
That's impossible!
It's the truth!
いいや
信仰は 必ずや人の苦境を救い…
Faith never fails to get us out of a bind!
And...
Welcome Back
（聖(せい)）あっ…
Yes!
（コンタ）やった！ やったぞ！
（岡崎(おかざき)）フゥ～！
We did it!
Woo-hoo!
We can do this...
（トマオ）やれる… やれるぞ！
We can do it!
（計）ハァ… ハァハァ…
Kei...
（加藤）け… 計ちゃん
（岡崎）殺せー！
（トマオ）やれー！
Kill him!
Do it!
（岡崎）殺せ 殺せ！
Kill him! Kill him!
計ちゃん！
Kei!
（岡崎）殺せー！
Kill him!
That dude's great!
す… すげえぞ あいつ
We can do it! We can do it!
やれるぞ　やれる！
He...
彼…
（岸本）えっ？
He's gotten used to it, hasn't he?
（聖）慣れてるのね
That's not true!
（岸本）そんなことない
（聖）そう？
Oh?
How could he get used to...
to something like THIS?
（岸本）こんなの 慣れるなんて
Still, he seems the most likely to survive.
でも いちばん生き残れそうだけど
Kurono...
玄野(くろの)君は…
He's strong, and...
強いし
All right!
（コンタ）よっしゃー！
（トマオ）俺らにも やれるって
We can do this!
We got this! We got it! We got it!
いける いける いけるぜ！
The legs! Crush his legs!
（トマオ）脚だ！ 脚をつぶせ！
I'm gonna kill it! I'm gonna kill it!
（計）殺す 殺す！
I'm a hero! Nothing can beat me!
俺はヒーローだ！ 何にも負けねえ
This is where I belong! This world!
俺の生きる場所は ここだ
この世界だ！
（あばれんぼう星人）ぬん！
（風の音）
ウッ…
（トマオたち）ウワッ！
（加藤）ウッ… け… 計ちゃん！
Kei!
Umm... Excuse me.
（宮藤(みやふじ)）
あの… ちょっと いいですか？
（加藤）えっ？
（宮藤）見てる場合じゃないような
I don't think we should be
just watching like this.
I mean... Maybe we should go, too.
その… 僕たちも
行ったほうがいいんじゃないかと
What do you think?
どうですか？
あっ… そ… そうだな
I guess so...
Son of a bitch!
てめえ！
ぬん！
（風の音）
You're really pissing me off!
うっとうしいっつうの！
ウッ… ウワッ…
（ＪＪ）ウワーッ！
Are you okay?
だ… 大丈夫？
I've got the suit on. I'm fine.
（加藤）スーツ着てる　心配ない
ぬん！
Idiot! Stay back!
（北条(ほうじょう)）バカ！ 下がってろ！
あっ… やべえ
会話しちゃったじゃねえかよ
Shit. I just talked to her...
ウワッ！
That thing is predicting Kei's moves.
動きを読まれてる
計ちゃん 動き読まれてるぞ！
Kei! He can read your moves!
Stop, you son of a bitch!
止まれ この野郎！
止まれって言ってんだよ！
I said stop, damn it!
Ha! Look at you now!
ヘヘッ… ざまあみろ
Kei!
（加藤）計ちゃん！
（計）加藤 見ろ！ 止めてやったぜ
Kato, look! I stopped it!
（加藤）何やってんだ！
（計）えっ？
What are you doing?
脚を撃つのよ！ 脚を！
Shoot the legs! The legs!
Why are you trying to prove who's stronger?!
（北条）
力比べして どうすんだよ！
ぬん！
ウワッ！
Kurono!
玄野君！
（発射音）
Dammit! You're asking for it!
くそ… 上等じゃねえか！
あいつ…
（トマオ）強(つえ)えんだか弱(よえ)えんだか
That guy...
Is he strong or is he weak?
（聖）やった！
（加藤）まだ分かんねえ
It worked!
We don't know that yet!
Run!
逃げろ！
How come it's not weakening?
（北条）なんで弱らないんだ？
（宮藤）
ダメージは与えたはずなのに
Our blasts should've damaged it!
The legs! Go for the legs!
脚だ！ 脚 脚！
It dodged!
よけた！
（加藤）くそ…
Shit! He's been analyzing
our moves this whole time!
俺らの動き ずっと分析してたんだ
You're not goin' anywhere!
（計）そうは いかねえんだよ！
（発射音）
Yes!
（聖）やった！
（北条）今度はイケてるぜ
That oughtta do the trick.
Heh heh... Heh heh
ぬん…
What the?!
あっ… なに？
But we shot the leg!
（聖）ちょっと！ 脚撃ったのに！
（岸本）さっきのとは違うの？
You mean it's different from the other one?!
おい 倒れねえじゃんか
Hey, he ain't going down.
They'll take care of it... right?
あ… あいつらが
なんとかすっだろう
ぬん…
Get back! We're too close!
距離を開けろ　これじゃ近すぎて…
Kato!
（岸本）加藤君！
He knows our moves!
動きを読まれてる！
Kei! You gotta try something new!
計ちゃん 今までに
やってない攻めだ　できるか？
Can you do it?
Kei! You rock!
計ちゃん やっぱ すげえ！
Whatever, just shoot!
（計）何でもいい！
撃て撃て！ 撃ちまくれ！
Shoot! Keep shooting!
撃て！ 早く！
Shoot, quick!
He's amazing...
あいつ やっぱ すげえ
So which is it?
どっちなんだ？
Like I said, he IS amazing.
（コンタ）
だから やっぱ すげえって
ぬん…
く… くそ！ この野郎
Shit! You son of a bitch!
He's gonna be crushed!
（北条）あいつ つぶされるぞ！
スーツを着ていても あれじゃ…
He's got the suit on, but still...
（宮藤）
は… 早く撃ったほうが… 早く！
We'd better hurry up and shoot. Hurry!
But what if our aim's off and we shoot
him to pieces? What then?!
（北条）ヘタに撃って あいつまで
バラバラになったら どうする！
Make sure you shoot away from Kei!
計ちゃんから離れた場所なら！
The legs! Shoot the legs!
（聖）脚なら… 脚を撃つのよ！
（東郷(とうごう)）フゥ…
We did it!
（岡崎たち）やったー！
Way to go!
That was awesome!
Look at that!
（コンタ）いいぞ！ ハハハハッ…
（トマオ）マジすげえよ！
Awesome!
（コンタ）
ざまあねえぜ ヘヘヘヘッ…
Look at you!
Ah, um...
あ… あの…
（トマオ）うん？
Huh?
Kei...
（加藤）計ちゃん… あっ…
フフッ… おかえり
Welcome back.
ヒャッホー！ アハハッ…
（発射音）
（岡崎）ほら！ ハハハハッ…
Hey, fat ass! Shut the hell up!
（トマオ）そこのデブ
うぜえんだよ！ 止まれ バカ！
Enough's enough, dipshit!
So it was you, huh?
（加藤）あんたか？
（聖）生きて戻れるかもって
言ってたよね？
You said we might be able to
make it back alive, right?
Huh? Oh. Yeah...
If we do make it back alive,
（聖）生きて戻れたらさ
私たち つきあわない？
you wanna go out with me?
（聖）ダ… あっ ダメ？ ヤダ？
No? You don't want to?
I... I really do think you're great.
（岸本）
私… 玄野君 すごいって思ってる
I'm serious.
ホントに…
加藤君とは感じが違うけど
You're a lot different from Kato, but...
Sure.
（計）いいよ
If you don't mind going out with ME...
俺で いいならさ
（聖）ホント？
Really?
Okay, then it's decided.
よし 決まりね
I just got my license, so
I'll take you out for a drive.
免許 取りたてだけど
ドライブ連れてったげる
Yeah.
You hit it from so far away.
You're a great shot.
あんな遠くから命中させるとは
すごい腕だな
What is this thing?
これは何なんだ？
What kind of creature is this?
何だ？ この生物は
Check it out...
あれ！
（コンタ）はぁ？
Huh?
What should we do? Hey, it's coming this way!
（コンタ）
どうするよ？ おい　こっち来るぜ
Ya think it's pissed at us?
（トマオ）
怒られるんかな？ 俺たち
He's one tough guy...
つわものだぜ あいつは
（宮藤）えっ？
Why's that fat ass looking at me like that?
なんで あのデブ
俺のほう見てんだ？ 気色悪い
He's creeping me out.
Maybe he's gay. You ARE cute, after all.
ホモなんじゃないの？
あんた かわいいから
He's gay?
ホモかよ
He can do things like that
because he's wearing the suit.
彼はスーツを着てるから
あれだけのことができるんだよ
Well, you're wearing one, too.
お前だって着てるじゃねえかよ
お前 何かできんのか？
What can YOU do?
Now that you mention it, last time he
killed most of them without the suit.
（北条）そういえば あいつ―
前回は
スーツなしで ほとんど倒したな
（岡崎）へえ…
Whoa.
Give me a break.
勘弁してくれよ
ホモは… モホはよ
Enough with the gay stuff, already.
So what do we do?
（トマオ）どうする？
Well, it's pretty small. We might be
able to take care of it.
（コンタ）
でも 小せえし なんとかなるかも
Small? That thing's over six feet!
（トマオ）“小せえ”って
２メートル超えてるぜ こいつ
What I mean is, it's smaller than that last one.
（コンタ）いや
さっきのヤツより小せえかなって
Should we call the others?
（トマオ）あいつら 呼ぶ？
Nah, it's okay. I'll take care of it.
（コンタ）
いいよ　こいつ 俺 やってやっから
（仏像星人）
ぬしらは してんのだもぬて
ぜんにするふさわかろう
You shall split the strands of your hair
Hair that even the four emperors let down
and wore touching their faces
The black which you will untie in the daytime
Shall be its true black at night
ひじゃむぬる くろまにまに
みずらに はにぬのだろう
Tied to the side
As cloth for your cheeks
Oh, man. It's started talking nonsense.
（トマオ）あ～あ…
意味 分かんねえこと言い始めた
I'll let you handle it.
任したかんね
（加藤）岸本さん？
Miss... Kishimoto.
えっ？
（加藤）あの…
Um...
あっ…
（加藤）岸本さん？
Miss Kishimoto?
あの…
（加藤）うん？
Uh...
Just "Kishimoto" is fine.
“岸本”で いいから
That's what you called me earlier.
さっきも そう言ってくれたよね？
Oh, uh... I did?
（加藤）あ… ああ そうだっけ？
岸本で いい
Just call me Kishimoto.
Anyway, could you take care of the
sniping next time, too?
（加藤）
じゃ 次も また狙撃 頼むよ
（コンタ）おっと…
Dude, awesome! Get him!
（トマオ）すげえ！ やれー！
（犬のほえる声）
Jesus...
ジーザス…
We all start out as pure and innocent babes
Even if you taste the bitter fruit,
don't be discouraged, walk straight
I know it's in the past, but the rain still stings
I'm lonely as floating ice
I kiss your thin finger
And remember you crying
Even if this is the end
I won't forget your last kiss
I won't forget
I won't forget his kiss
It's big, but it's just a Buddhist statue, right?
（岡崎）“でかい”ったって
たかが大仏だろう？
We've got a whole bunch of guns over here,
and we're gonna shoot the shit out 'em!
こっちには銃が山ほどあんだよ
好き勝手に ぶっ放せるんだぜ
I don't wanna die... I don't wanna die!
死にたくない　死にたくない…
Next episode...
次回 “なんじゃ ありゃあっ”
"What the hell is that?!"